seasiainfotech.com 2016-06-30

# Privacy Policy - Seasia Infotech

**Seasia Infotech**  
Access to and use of the Seasia Infotech Web Site is expressly conditioned upon agreement to the following policies and conditions:

**Copyright Statement**  
The text, graphics, photos, and other materials appearing on the Seasia Infotech Web site are the sole property of Seasia Infotech, Chandigarh, India, and are protected by copyright law and intellectual property law.

Seasia Infotech gives visitors permission to copy documents and other materials on this Web site for non-commercial uses within an individual organization only. Distribution, retrieval, storage or other use for commercial purposes is strictly prohibited without prior written permission from Seasia Infotech.

**Warranty**  
While every reasonable effort has been made to ensure current and accurate information on this Web site, the information is provided “as is”, “as available” without warranty of any kind, either express or implied, and does not constitute a legal contract between Seasia Infotech and any other person or entity unless otherwise specified. Information is subject to change at any time without prior notice.

Seasia makes no express or implied warranty regarding such information or data, and hereby expressly disclaims all legal liability and responsibility to persons or entities that use or access this site and its content, based on their reliance on any information or data that is available through this website.

Responsibility for content contained within personal home pages or Web sites to which the Seasia Infotech Web site links resides solely with the author of such sites. Seasia Infotech is not responsible for any errors that might appear therein. Moreover, views contained therein are strictly the opinions of the author and are not officially sanctioned by Seasia Infotech.

The content of this website is not designed or intended to provide authoritative financial, accounting, investment, or other professional advice which may be reasonably relied on by its readers. If expert assistance in this area is required, the services of a qualified professional should be sought.

This general disclaimer is in addition to, and not in lieu of, any other disclaimers found on pages, applications or programs within this site. In addition, the terms of this disclaimer extend to the Seasia, its directors, officers, and employees.

**Privacy Policy**  
Seasia Infotech uses the information you submit to us for the sole purpose of providing the service you requested. We do not share personally identifiable information about individual visitors with any other person or entity. Seasia Infotech generates reports about the volume of visitors, variety, timing and other non-personal statistical information about traffic to our Web site for internal use to provide a better site for our visitors.

We use reasonable precautions to keep any personal information collected secure and follow industry-standard precautions and procedures in the transmission and storage of electronic data. Specifically, Seasia Infotech Web site uses secure socket layer (SSL) encryption to process secure information allowing online users protection from interception of private information by any third party. However, we are not responsible for any breach of security resulting from an individual user’s computer security failures. Seasia Infotech links to a variety of other Web sites and is not responsible for their privacy policies, security or how they may handle any user information they may collect.

Use and Disclosure of Information Seasia Infotech Gathers through the Site.  
a. **Personal Information**. We may use your Personal Information in any of the following ways.

i. **Communications**. We encourage Visitors to contact us with questions and comments. Personal Information may be used in order to respond to your questions and comments.

ii. **Business Purposes**. We may also use your Personal Information for internal business purposes, such as analyzing and managing our businesses.

iii. **Transactions**. When you take part in a Transaction through the Site such as purchasing software, we may collect Payment Information from you related to such Transaction as well as other Personal Information. We may use your Personal Information or Payment Information in order to complete the Transaction and, if applicable, to fulfill your purchase. We may also provide such Payment Information to third parties as necessary to complete your Transaction (for example, to process your credit card).

iv. **Special Promotions and Product Information**. In addition, Seasia Infotech may use your Personal Information to provide you with email updates and announcements concerning our products and special promotions. You may opt-out of receiving these messages from us at any time.

v. **Critical Communications**. From time to time we may use your Personal Information to email you important information regarding the Site, your Transactions, or changes to our terms, conditions, and policies (“Critical Emails”). Because this information may be critical to your use of the Site, you may not opt-out of receiving these emails.

vi. **Third Party Service Providers**. We work with third parties who provide services, including web site hosting, credit card processing, and other administrative services. We may share your Personal Information, including your Payment Information, with such third parties for the purpose of enabling such third parties to provide such services.

vii. **Miscellaneous**. Finally, we may disclose your Personal Information if we believe that we are required to do so: (i) by law; (ii) to comply with legal process or governmental requests; (iii) to enforce our Terms of Service; (iv) to protect our operations; (v) to protect the rights, privacy, safety or property of Seasia Infotech, you or others; and (vi) to permit us to pursue available remedies or limit the damages that we may sustain.

b. **Aggregate Information**. We analyze Aggregate Information in order to enhance web site security, track the popularity of certain pages of the Site, the success of our email notifications, traffic levels on the Site and other usage data, all of which helps us to provide content tailored to your interests, improve the Site and related services and to otherwise enhance your experience on the Site. We may share Aggregate Information with Affiliated Entities and other third parties.

**Other Important Notes Regarding Our Privacy Practices**  
a. **Security**. We have security measures and tools in place to help protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. Any time you provide us with your credit card number, that credit card number is transmitted to us by your browser in an encrypted format using industry-standard, SSL (secure socket layer) encryption. No method of transmitting or storing data is completely secure. As a result, although we strive to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us through or in connection with the Site. If you have reason to believe that your interaction with us is no longer secure (for example, if you feel that the security of any account you might have with us has been compromised), you must immediately notify us of the problem by contacting us in accordance with “Contact Us,” .

b. **Assignment**. We reserve the right to transfer any and all information that we collect from users of the Site to a third party in the event of any merger, sale, joint venture, assignment, transfer or other disposition of all or any portion of Seasia assets or stock (including without limitation in connection with any bankruptcy or similar proceedings).  
**  
Remaketing** : We use Google Analytics remarketing codes to log when users view specific pages or take specific actions on a website. This allows us to provide targeted advertising in the future. If you do not wish to receive this type of advertising from us in the future you can opt out using the [DoubleClick opt-out page](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb#display_optout) or the Network [Advertising Initiative opt-out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)

**Changes to This Policy**  
Seasia Infotech reserves the right to change this Policy, and any of our policies or procedures concerning the treatment of information collected through the Site, without prior notice. Any changes to our Policy will become effective upon posting of the revised Policy on the Internet, accessible through the Site. Use of the Site following such changes constitutes your acceptance of the revised Policy then in effect. We encourage you to bookmark this page and to periodically review it to ensure familiarity with the most current version of our Policy.

This Policy represents the sole, authorized statement of Seasia Infotech practices with respect to the collection of Personal Information (defined above) through the Site and Seasia’s use of such information. Any summaries of this Policy generated by third party software or otherwise (for example, in connection with the Platform for Privacy Preferences or “P3P”) shall have no legal effect, do not bind Seasia Infotech, shall not be relied upon in substitute for this Policy, and neither supersede nor modify this Policy.
